BANK = [
  {
  question: 'Who directed the 1993 haunting hit "The Exorcist?"',
  answers: ['William Peter Blatty',
  'William Friedkin',
  'Alfred Hitchcock',
  'John Carpenter'],
  correctAnswer: 'William Friedkin',
},
{
  question: 'Who is the murderous antagonist in the original "Friday the 13th?"',
  answers: ['Freddy Kreuger',
  'Jason Voorhees',
  'Pamela Voorhees',
  'Pinhead'],
  correctAnswer: 'Pamela Voorhees',
},
{
  question: 'What city, formerly named Blair, was the Blair Witch Project set in?',
  answers: ['Burkittsville',
  'Salem',
  'Poughkeepsie',
  'Translyvania'],
  correctAnswer: 'Burkittsville',
},
{
  question: `What year did John Carpenter's cult classic "The Thing" come out?`,
  answers: ['1988',
  '1985',
  '1979',
  '1982'],
  correctAnswer: '1982',
},
{
  question: `What is the name for the fully-matured creature from Ridley Scott's "Alien"?`,
  answers: ['Xenomorph',
  'Protohuman',
  'E.T.',
  'Predator'],
  correctAnswer: 'Xenomorph',
},
{
  question: `What is the name of the hotel that was the setting for Stanley Kubrick (and Stephen King)'s "The Shining"?`,
  answers: ['The Grand Hotel',
  'The Overlook Hotel',
  'Bates Hotel',
  'Hotel California'],
  correctAnswer: 'The Overlook Hotel',
},
{
  question: `How many "A Nightmare On Elm Street" movies are there in total?`,
  answers: ['5',
  '3',
  '7',
  '8'],
  correctAnswer: '8',
},
{
  question: `Which famous slasher series features a killer in a William Shatner mask?`,
  answers: ['Scream',
  'I Know What You Did Last Summer',
  'Halloween',
  'Psycho'],
  correctAnswer: 'Halloween',
},
{
  question: `In which zombie movie are the protagonists stuck in a shopping mall?`,
  answers: ['Night of the Living Dead',
  'Dawn of the Dead',
  '28 Days Later',
  'Resident Evil'],
  correctAnswer: 'Dawn of the Dead',
},
{
  question: `What was the first horror film to be nominated for a Best Picture Oscar?`,
  answers: ['The Exorcist',
  "Rosemary's Baby",
  'The Omen',
  'The Texas Chainsaw Massacre'],
  correctAnswer: 'The Exorcist',
}
]
